lovelandia.com 2011-12-04

# LoveLandia Privacy Policy

We are glad to welcome you on [Lovelandia.com](http://www.lovelandia.com/) site. This privacy statement is subjected to You in order to ensure that our site is committed to secure the privacy of our members' details. Please take your time to read through this Privacy Statement to see our privacy position. 

What information do we collect?

As our site provides you with opportunity not just to post poetry but to create your personal profile and use our dating services, thus we may require from You some information that may be considered as personally identifiable. 

Registration information

You will provide us the following information about yourself: 

  * username
  * password
  * e-mail address
  * date of birth
  * country
  * city
  * postal code
  * postal code
  * short biography

All these information is obligatory and you should provide it carefully. In no way any personal information will be used for commercial marketing purposes or will be available to some third-party individuals or organizations. 

Other personal information that we could possibly need

Due to a great amount of dating scam, to protect our members we may require from You the copy of Your passport or any other document identifying personality. If You do not wish to provide us with such kind of document our site reserves the right to delete Your personal profile. 

This Privacy Statement does not apply to websites that may be linked to LoveLandia.com. We recommend You to read that site's privacy statement before using it. 

Under our terms of use members are allowed to post any kind of poetry or prose unless it is stolen. Members should avoid any kind of ethnically or otherwise objectionable content. On a Submission Policy page you will get more detailed information on submission terms and conditions. 

The LoveLandia.com site is an open and free web site in all respects and meanings, but any of your confidential information is closed to others and strongly guarded. 

Copyrights

All Lovelandia.com site contents (except for members' submissions) copyrights are reserved by Lovelandia.com and content copying and duplicating are strongly prohibited. Copyright of content submitted by Lovelandia.com visitors belongs to respective submitters. 

Lovelandia.com does not lay any claims to works submitted to be its own. As all works are gathered from numerous resources we do not claim to the initial ownership of neither work of art nor any poetic image posted on our site. If you are the original author of any work and want it to be removed from our site, please contact us with your copyrights notification and we'll remove it immediately. 

Under this Privacy Statement we declare that Lovelandia.com does not come within any liability for the content posted on our site is used by third party companies or individuals for their purposes, thus breaching your copyrights or for the information or photos posted or uploaded on our site by our members be unique. 

Acceptance of agreements

By reading this You agree to our Privacy Statement. If You do not agree You may not use this site. 

We may update our Privacy Statement from time to time so please visit this page regularly.
